thehumansolution.com 2017-03-10

# We take your privacy seriously | The Human Solution

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

#### We Care About Your Privacy

We know how important it is to keep your personal information confidential, especially when shopping online. We are committed to protecting your privacy. The Privacy Policy outlined below informs you of what information we collect when you visit and shop at The Human Solution, and how we use that information.

#### Section 1: What do we do with your information?

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computerâ€™s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

**Email marketing**

With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

#### Section 2: Consent

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only. If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

**How do I withdraw my consent?**

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at info@thehumansolution.com or mailing us at: SquareGrove LLC, 2139 W Anderson Ln, Austin, TX, 78757, United States.

#### Section 3: Disclosure

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our [Terms of Service.](http://www.thehumansolution.com/terms-of-service.html)

#### Section 4: Yahoo

Our store is hosted by Yahoo. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. Your data is stored through Yahoo's data storage, databases and the general Yahoo application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall. For more insight, you may also want to read Yahoo's [Terms of Service here](https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/terms/utos/index.htm) or [ Privacy Statement here.](https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/index.htm)

#### Section 5: Third-Party Services

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers. In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located. As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act. Once you leave our storeâ€™s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our websiteâ€™s Terms of Service.

**Links**

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

**Payments**

All payments are processed through a service provided by PayPal. For more information on PayPal, visit [www.paypal.com](http://www.paypal.com/)

#### Section 6: Security

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) for all financial transactions through our site, as well as SSL encryption to protect your personal details. We use reputable and established third-party providers for the security of our servers. While we make every effort to protect you, please note that it is impossible to guarantee 100% complete security, whether shopping online or offline.

**Cookies**

We use browser cookies to gain information about customers' shopping experiences, and to deliver remarketing advertisements online. You may adjust your browser to reject cookies, in which case our site will be unable to deliver remarketing ads or recognize your cart or your account, if you choose to register an account. You can shop and purchase as a guest, without signing up for an account.

#### Section 7: Age of Consent

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

#### Section 8: Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it. If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

#### Contact Information 

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this privacy policy.   
Our Internet address is [http://www.thehumansolution.com](http://www.thehumansolution.com/)   
You may contact us by e-mail at [info@thehumansolution.com](mailto:info@thehumansolution.com)   
You may contact us by phone at **800-531-3746**

**SquareGrove, LLC - The Human Solution**   
2139 W Anderson Ln   
Austin, TX 78757-1221   
United States 

Copyright 2003 - 2020 by SquareGrove, LLC. All rights reserved.
